{
    "id": "3cd0250a0f4d4e4ab10ed5d0a6b2d476",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Come And Cut",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ce4689e8b3cf49f2ac4732a36642a313",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Come And Cut",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Pull hard and the two pieces will come …………………..",
                    "description": "When things come apart, they separate.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "apart",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I came ………………. an old friend of mine yesterday.",
                    "description": "To come across somebody is to meet them unexpectedly.",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "through",
                        "across"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I came ………………. with typhoid last month.",
                    "description": "To come down with typhoid is to become sick with typhoid.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "off",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The watchman came …………….. with all the evidences he could collect.",
                    "description": "To come forward is to volunteer for a task.",
                    "answers": [
                        "forward",
                        "out",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you want to lose weight, you should cut ……………… cheese and burgers.",
                    "description": "To cut back on something is to consume less of it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "down",
                        "out",
                        "down on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We had to cut many trees …………….. to build the house.",
                    "description": "To cut something down is to make it fall to the ground.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "down",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Julie cut …………… while I was chatting with her friend.",
                    "description": "To cut in is to interrupt.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "in",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The air conditioner will cut ……………… when the room temperature reaches 26 degree Celsius.",
                    "description": "When a machine or engine cuts in, it starts operating.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "in",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The doctors cut ……………….. his legs to save his life.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The utility company cut ……………… our power supply because we hadn’t paid the bill.",
                    "description": "To cut off power is to stop providing it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "off",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "His parents cut him ………….. when he married against their wishes.",
                    "description": "To cut somebody off is to take them out of a will.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "off",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I cut these pictures ………………. of a magazine.",
                    "description": "To cut something out is to remove it with scissors.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "out",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}